RIZKY MASHUDI Software Developer

Batam, Indonesia | HP: 082285388898 | Email: <u>rizkymashudi7@gmail.com</u> https://rizkymashudi.github.io/rmwashere/

SUMMARY

Currently learning and interested in iOS development and related technology, I have less than 2 years of experience as an associate laravel developer, developing a cms backend for mobile games. The achievement I got while working was being able to integrate cms with aws web services and google playstore in-app purchases.

EXPERIENCE

Apple Developer Academy Infinite Learning – Batam, Indonesia

Internship (February 2021 – December 2021)

- Perform investigation when going to solve a problem.
- Implement design thinking and User-centered design in developing an application.
- Implement design based on HIG or design guidelines from apple.
- Implement basic UX research skills such as domain research, solution concept, app statement, user persona, user journey mapping, affinity mapping, and concept testing.
- Implement basic UI design such as making lo-fid, hi-fid, prototyping, user testing, and usability testing.
- Implement basic skills swift, mvc, auto layout, and localization in application development using the framework provided by apple.
- Learn and implement professional skills such as elevator speech, storybeat, teamwork, project management, empathy, and agile development.

PT Asta Satria Investama – Batam, Indonesia

Assoicate Laravel developer (September 2019 – February 2021)

- Develop features based on the brief and backlog provided by the project lead.
- Debugging based on tickets from the QA team
- Optimizing features, and updating dependencies used in the project.

PT Shimano – Batam, Indonesia

Operator (July 2015 - July 2017)

Conduct screening process on products that are being produced.

EDUCATION

Politeknik Negeri Batam (2017 - 2021)

D3 Informatics Engineering

SOFT SKILLS

- Teamwork
- Presentation
- People management
- Keynote

- Agile development
- Qualitative and quantitative riset
- Usability testing
- Research

HARD SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- JS
- PHP
- Laravel

- React js
- Node is
- Swift
- Sketch
- Figma